Starting to feel guaranteed as far as 9z are concerned.
对 9z 来说，这局开始像是稳了。
Never wants to celebrate early, but at 12-1,
一般谁都不想太早庆祝，但 12 比 1 这种比分
when it truly has felt like they could do no wrong,
而且他们这张图几乎怎么打都对的时候，
they've just got it wrapped already.
看起来真的已经十拿九稳了。
Coupled with the absence of
再加上
all of the Falcons here on the decider map.
Falcons 在这张决胜图上几乎全员隐身。
These guys nuts? Do they not have a kit?
这帮人疯了吗？他们难道没钳子吗？
They do not have a kit.
他们真没钳子。
They've got an AWP.
但他们手里有把大狙。
And they've got the opening kill.
而且还拿到了首杀。
NiKo never sees that one coming.
NiKo 完全没料到这一枪。
No chance you'd be ready for that.
这根本不可能提前防到。
kyousuke, 30 health, scout.
kyousuke 只剩 30 血，手里还是鸟狙。
m0NESY on the walkout middle.
m0NESY 正往中路摸出去。
kyousuke is gonna get swept away by luchov,
kyousuke 会被 luchov 直接收掉，
as m0NESY tries to chase it outwards.
而 m0NESY 还想继续往外追。
DGT looks to get into the play,
DGT 也准备加入战局，
but don't jump on it just yet.
但先别急着下结论。
you will get bested by DGT,
你要是硬接，还真会被 DGT 压过去，
that's TeSeS with the bomb out middle.
而且中路带包的是 TeSeS。
And a cat play coming through from Karrigan,
同时 Karrigan 还从小道展开动作，
off a Desert Eagle,
手里只有一把沙鹰。
held still by meyern,
不过被 meyern 卡住了，
and HUASOPEEK
而且 HUASOPEEK
flanks, and 9z...
还在侧翼绕后，9z 这边……
So now the Falcons are staring at
这样一来，Falcons 就得面临
three matches to try and secure the playoffs.
还要再打三场，才有机会去争季后赛席位。
It is MOUZ, Spirit,
现在 2 比 0 组里有 MOUZ、Spirit，
FURIA and 9z in the 2-0 pool tomorrow.
还有 FURIA 和 9z，明天都在 2 比 0 组。